When they come in, we treat it just like one of us, okay?
That's one of us.
Google, gobble, one of us.
We accept that one of us. Google, gobble, one of us.
Jordan!
Your dad's coming. Something about the American Express bill?
Can you get him out of here?
Yeah, lick my toe.
No, I'm serious. Get...
Fuck. Okay, guys, act like we're working.
Got any fucking stock?
Okay, where were you? He's coming. He's coming.
Make some shit up.
So I think it would be short Pfizer.
$430,000 in one month, Jordy? Huh?
Four hundred and fucking...
$30,000 fucking dollars in one fucking month!
Good morning. They're business expensive. Relax.
Business expenses?
Yes.
Jordy, look what you got here.
What?
Look at this. $26,000 for one fucking dinner!
Okay, no, no, no. This could be explained.
Dad, we had clients. We had Pfizer clients.
Right, the Porter House from Argentina.
The expensive champagne and the wine.
We had to buy champagne.
And you go out at all the fucking sides.
Tell them about the sides, Jordy.
I ordered the sides, so...
Sides? Sides? $26,000 worth of sides?
What are these sides? Did cure cancer?
The sides did cure cancer. That's the problem.
That's why they were expensive.
Shut the fuck up. Stop.
I'm serious. I know.
E.J. Entertainment.
What the fuck is E.J. Entertainment?
Well, that's, uh...
Yeah, Jord, what's E.J. Entertainment?
How do I describe this?
Jord, what is that?
It's a fucking prostitution ring, Jordy.
I know.
That's what it is.
That's... That is what it is.
Isn't that the perfect description for it?
That is what it is.
But none of these were charged to me.
This is all of them.
Oh, that was all us.
It wasn't me, though.
Fucking explain this shit to him.
These are all of your fucking charges right here.
You guys, the IRS, they allow for T&A. It's fine.
T&A. T&A.
Yeah. I said T&A.
No, no, you said T&A.
No, I didn't.
Yeah, you did.
Why did I say that?
You said T&A. It's T&A.
I know you're upset about the dinner,
and that makes sense because we did spend too much money,
but I said T&A.
Don't tell me what you said. I heard what you said.
Dad, he said T&A.
He did. He said T&A.
Yeah, absolutely. No question. I heard it.
I'm trying to...
I'm getting this close.
That's what I'm saying.
I want you to open up more, Max.
He's gonna fucking kill you.
Why do you hold it in?
Why do you...
Max, Max, why do you hold it in?
That's it. That's it.
Get the fuck out of here.
No, no, no, no.
Get out of here.
What kind of hooker takes credit cards?
A rich one.
At Stratton.